# William Pleasant

Chino Hills, CA

jgatz33@yahoo.com - 909-247-9670

I am an individual focused on results. I've been in the retail industry for over 5 years selling different products. I've grown to really love my customers and I'll do anything to win and earn their business, because it's my business to make numbers and attain repeat customers for wherever I'm working.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Sales Associate**

Howard's Appliance Flat Screen - Alhambra, CA - August 2013 to Present

Responsibilities

Retail

100% Commission based face to face selling, pitching and doing demo's on all our products, extended service policies, making and exceeding bi-weekly quotas, follow up after the sale, also sold to large accounts (landlords, apartment owners etc) All the salesmen were excellent in customer service for we handled everything and did whatever we had to do to make the sale stick.

#### **Financial Credit Advisor**

Bank Of America - December 2012 to June 2013

December 2012- June 2013

I was trained heavily on financial services, especially the credit sector. Learned various laws and was on the phone helping customers. During training I was awarded team player of the floor.

Commissioned Sales

### **Sales Associate**

Howard's Appliance & Flat Screen - La Habra, CA - August 2009 to July 2012

La Habra, CA

Retail

100% Commission based face to face selling, pitching and doing demo's on all our products, extended service policies, making and exceeding bi-weekly quotas, follow up after the sale, also sold to large accounts (landlords, apartment owners etc) All the salesmen were excellent in customer service for we handled everything and did whatever we had to do to make the sale stick.

## Sales Associate

Select Comfort Retail Corporation - Rancho Cucamonga, CA - February 2008 to July 2009

Retail

Sold big ticket Sleep Number beds, used different technologies to do our demo's for the customers, established relationships with our customers as a sale was not always made instantly, responsible for generating our own leads daily, and meeting monthly sales goals.

#### **Sales Associate**

Sears and Roebuck - Brea, CA - July 2007 to January 2008

Retail

Advanced product knowledge in the refrigeration department, heavy emphasis on selling expensive extended warranties, meeting sales goals monthly, follow up service after the sale and overall customer service.

## **Seasonal Sales Associate**

Circuit City - Brea, CA - October 2006 to January 2007

Retail

Product knowledge in the small electronics/TV departments, making sales, stocking, ringing sales, customer services.

## **Customer Service**

Quiznos - Brea, CA - May 2005 to February 2006

Food and Beverage Production

Made Sandwiches, prepped the food, ringing sales, cleaning/stocking.

#### **Sales Associate**

Howard's Appliance Flat Screen - Alhambra, CA

**EDUCATION** 

## **High School Diploma in business**

Mount San Antonio College - Walnut, CA September 2002 to June 2006

Diamond Bar High School